Automatic window display
The window display is the basis for automatic window display function.
Move the mouse to the 3D window to display the virtual model.
Click to display the virtual model window display.
You can see that the virtual model's body surface is covered with a layer of natural invisible clothing.
It will not directly affect the clothing you make,
but through the model body data contained in it,
it can help you quickly adjust the size of the clothing to adapt to multiple virtual models of different bodies.
The virtual model worn by Marvelous Designer is worn with a window display.
If the virtual model you import from the outside does not have window display information,
you can automatically create a window display when you import it.
When the standard A-Pose or T-Pose model is imported to Marvelous Designer,
it can automatically generate window display information.
If you want to create a window display,
you may not be satisfied with the effect of the window display.
Or sometimes,
because the pose is special,
or the human body recognition is accurate when A-Pose or T-Pose is used,
it may fail to create a window display.
At this time, you need to define and edit your window display.
Click on the virtual model image in the menu bar.
Click on the virtual model editor.
Then switch to the window display label page.
You can see that there are some purple measurement lines on the model body.
In contrast to the visual image,
check if there are purple measurement lines that are not perfectly identified or cannot be identified.
You can click on the name of the part that needs to be modified.
Add a purple measurement line to the model body.
The original measurement line on the part will be replaced with the measurement line you have defined.
After the check is complete, click on the window display.
The model body is covered with a layer of window display.
If there is a gap between the window screen and the model body,
you can pull it out a little bit.
The model body and the model are translated into .apt.
Next time, you can directly call the model that contains the window display information.
The window display information will also be stored on the clothing.
Open the clothing window display.
You can see that the clothing is also covered with a red window display.
Press Shift A to display the virtual model Hanna that we have already opened in advance.
Let's try the virtual model function in the 3D window.
You can see that the clothes are worn on the virtual model.
But this function will not automatically adjust the clothes to fit the model.
It just automatically wears the clothes.
So the clothes may look too tight or loose.
Press Alt-6 to check the hard drive.
You can see that the clothes are too loose.
Press G to return to the previous step.
You can increase the particle diameter of the clothes before computing.
You can make the calculation speed faster.
This time, we try to operate the automatic adjustment of the panel in the 2D window.
Press C to select these functions.
You can see that the panel has been changed.
The clothing line is now more in harmony with the virtual model.
We will see you next time.
Thank you for watching.